[Music]
English listening test part six designed
for A2
Learners this test consists of 20
questions which are divided into four
parts I will give you a short
instruction at the beginning of each
part before we get started take a pen
and paper so you can take notes while
listening are you ready
let's get
started part one listen to Tom talking
about his awkward experience in a
beautiful house and be ready to answer
the true or false
questions I had always been an average
guy living an ordinary life but one day
everything changed I won the lottery
jackpot and suddenly I became a
millionaire I couldn't believe my luck
and was overjoyed to be able to live a
luxurious life I decided to buy a huge
house and move in right away it was a
beautiful property with a sprawling lawn
a massive swimming pool in a tennis
court I had never seen anything like it
before and felt like I was living in a
dream however things took a turn for the
worse when strange things began to
happen I started to experience things
like doors slamming shut on their their
own Footsteps in the hallways and
objects moving without explanation I
started to feel like I wasn't alone in
the house and it was starting to scare
me one night I was in my bedroom when I
heard a knock on the door when I opened
it there was no one there I returned to
bed but the knocking continued growing
louder and more
repetitive finally I got up and opened
the door only to find a ghostly figure
standing in front of me the figure told
me that the house was cursed and that I
needed to leave immediately I was
terrified and fled the house that same
night I never returned and sold the
house soon
after true or
[Music]
false
part two listen to to five conversations
and be ready to complete the
sentences hey Martin do you want to go
to the movies tonight maybe what time
how about the 9:15 show oh that's too
late for me I usually go to bed at 8:30
so early yeah I have to get up at 5:00
a.m. to study before school 5:00 a.m.
why don't you study at night I don't
like to stay up late I'm a morning
person you look tired Jessica yeah well
I'm usually tired really what time do
you go to bed often around midnight I
like to stay up late but I have to get
up at 6:15 to go to
work do you want to go running tomorrow
morning Anna it depends what time how
about
7:00 7:00 I don't get up until around 9:
wow you get a lot of sleep not really I
usually stay until about 2: in the
morning are you a morning person or a
night person George oh definitely a
night person really yeah I can't fall
asleep before midnight I usually go to
bed around 1:00 a.m. huh do you sleep
late in the morning not really I usually
get up at A4 to
8 did you watch the 11:00 news last
night Betty no I was asleep I usually go
to bed around 10 10:00 that's pretty
early isn't it yeah well I'd like to
stay up later but I have to get up at
6:00 a.m. to go to
work choose the correct
option
[Music]
I
part three listen to a conversation and
be ready to answer the true or false
questions could you help me please sure
what's the trouble I think the cooling
system leaks or something is wrong with
the water pump the engine probably
overheated let me take a
look I hope you can fix
it well I don't think I can do it today
I'll probably have to order a new water
pump for it you mean I can't use my car
no I'm afraid not by the way you look
familiar ma'am so do you my name's
Michael Roberts
Roberts do you have a younger brother
named
James yes I do he's a student of mine oh
then you must be Miss White his biology
teacher yes I am I'm glad to meet you
glad to meet you too so can I give you a
ride to somewhere well I don't know are
you sure it's no trouble no not at all
well thanks I appreciate it so let's
hurry please it's getting late okay let
me get the
keys true or
[Music]
false
part four listen to a street interview
and be ready to complete the
sentences
hello can I ask you a few questions yes
of course first of all what's your name
and where do you come from my name is
Anita I'm from Mumbai India after
getting married we moved to Delhi and
why are you here in the United States
well I'm here mainly because I want to
improve my English how much English did
you know before you came
not a lot I studied English at school
but I didn't learn much now I'm studying
in a language school here which school
Manhattan Language School great your
English is very good now who's your
teacher thank you very much my teacher
is called Mr Johnson he's great what did
you do back in India well actually I
wanted to be a language teacher but my
English was not good enough then I
became an art teacher I taught children
from 12 to 16 how many children were in
your
classes sometimes as many as 50 goodness
that's a lot how often do you go back
home I go home twice a year in my
holidays that's great I hope you have a
wonderful time here thank
you choose the correct
option
[Music]
take
don't forget to share your score in the
comments
section if you haven't taken our
previous listening tests yet the
playlist link is in the description
below if you're new here be sure to
subscribe because more valuable content
is on the way see you in our up upcoming
videos